initially when i sat down to create this video i was thinking about giving it a fancy ass title
something like in defense of amanda seals and angel reese but then i realized why do i need to
make a video in defense of these black women because to say that they needed to be defended
would suggest that they did something wrong and they didn't so i want to change my motivation
and this video is in support of amazing black women like angel reese and amanda seals but
particularly any black woman that you may find yourself thinking she's a bit of a dick
full stop and the truth of the matter is if you run upon a black woman that you think is
disagreeable or potentially a dick or even perceive her as a dick that took a lot of work
let me tell you what i mean when i think about the patriarchy it teaches women across race and
ethnicities right to be nice not kind those are not the same thing right niceness is the performance
of agreeability it is a likability it is pretending to be something that you're usually not just so
people can give you favor right then there's the supremacy project which prioritize white racialized
folks in general but in particular white womanhood for surveillance and breeding purposes we'll get
into that in another day if we need to then there's global anti-blackness that teaches people across the
african diaspora that we don't have humanity let alone any type of social value or worth so why would
we ask people to see us and give us dignity right and then what's really ironic is that there is a
woman feminist project that exists that black women and all types of women have tried to locate
themselves in but in those in those spaces we're consistently being reminded that there is a pecking
order into which women's concerns and issues are addressed or even heard so altogether all these
systems and ideologies work in tandem to actually keep black women really silent right so that means that
if you find a black woman who's very articulate about the shit that she don't like it's because she's
done work against the status quo to be able to tell you what she doesn't like and the energy around her
disagreeability should just be a actual actual gratitude that she felt safe enough to tell you
how she felt in the first day in place